(Leonard(on screen):)And now that I think about it,
(Leonard(on screen):)I bet a lot of you
feel the same way.
(Leonard(on screen):)So, for the remainder
of my speech,
(Leonard(on screen):)this is for the invisible kids.
(Leonard(on screen):)Uh, maybe you never fit in.
(Leonard(on screen):)Or maybe you're
the smallest kid in the school,
(Leonard(on screen):)or the heaviest or the weirdest.
(Leonard(on screen):)Maybe you're graduating
(Leonard(on screen):)and you still haven't had
your first kiss.
By the way, 19;
(Leonard(on screen):)and Geraldine Coco,
wherever you are, thank you.
(Leonard(on screen):)Maybe you don't have
any friends.
(Leonard(on screen):)And guess what? That's okay.
(Leonard(on screen):)While all the popular kids
are off doing--
(Leonard(on screen):)whatever, I don't know
what they were doing
(Leonard(on screen):)'cause I was never there...
I'll-I'll tell you later.
(Leonard:)My point is,
(Leonard:)while you're spending
all this time on your own,
(Leonard:)building computers
or practicing your cello,
(Leonard:)what you're really doing
is becoming interesting.
(Leonard:)And when people finally
do notice you,
(Leonard:)they're gonna find someone
a lot cooler than they thought.